batuk.in 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy | Batuk.in

### 1\. Terms

By accessing the web site at [http://batuk.in](http://batuk.in/), you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.

### 2\. Use License

  1. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Batuk.in’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: 
    1. modify or copy the materials;
    2. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
    3. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Batuk.in’s web site;
    4. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
    5. transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
  2. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Batuk.in at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

### 3\. Disclaimer

  1. The information provided or published on Batuk.in is “as is” and we do not change or modify any detail of the Actual Information given by Officials. However, we update the content in our own language with a purpose to make it easier for readers (students, candidates). Moreover, Batuk.in does not claim to stick with the words given in any post/article and the website or team of Batuk.in is not responsible for the same.

### 4\. Limitations

In no event shall Batuk.in or its team are responsible for any damage caused by misunderstanding on the candidate’s end or vice versa. The content upload on our website Batuk.in are not manipulated in any terms. However, due to changes made by the Official Authorities of particular University, Institution, Board and Commission, the website Batuk.in will not be responsible for any misleading or harm suffered to any person. The readers must check the Official Advertisement/Notice or website for confirmation of such information and updates regarding the same.

### 5\. Revisions and Errata

The materials appearing on Batuk.in’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Batuk.in does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Batuk.in may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Batuk.in does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

### 6\. Links

Batuk.in has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Batuk.in of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.

### 7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications

Batuk.in may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

### 8\. Governing Law

Any claim relating to Batuk.in’s web site shall be governed by the laws of Gujarat, India without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.

Your privacy is important to us, and it is Batuk.in’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.

At batuk.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by batuk.in and how it is used. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, batuk.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
batuk.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on batuk.in.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to batuk.in and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….

**Google AdSense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on batuk.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

batuk.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. batuk.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Batuk.in may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Batuk.in’s sole discretion.
